It's cute.
かわいいね
Were you able to take a break?
休憩できた?
yes.
はい
I was asking you to give me a break.
休憩させてくれって言ってたもんだよ
how was it?
どうだった?
The butt from earlier.
さっきのお尻
successfully.
うまく
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
Was it tough?
きつかった?
It was amazing.
くりしかった
Was it vivid?
くりしかった?
I see.
そっか
I think you'll feel better as you do it.
やっていくうちに、 気持ちよくなると思うから
I'll put my dick in it.
僕のおちんちん入れるから
terrible?
やばい?
terrible.
やばい
good luck.
頑張ってね
It's huge.
で っかい
huge?
でっかい?
Well then, give me your butt next time.
じゃあ、今度お尻つきだしてくれ
You're throwing up a lot.
しっかり吐いてるね
My butt is a bit full, though.
お尻はちょっと、 まあ、ふさがってるけど
Let's go.
行けよ
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
If this big guy messes with me, I'll go.
このでっかくにいじられたら行くんだ
Go again.
もう一回行って
That's amazing.
すごいね
Please, just leave it at that.
どうぞ、そのまましてくれ
There are two things in there.
2つのが入っちゃってるね
copper?
どう?
This feeling.
この感じ
Spread your legs.
広げて、足広げて
It's really tied up.
すごい縛ってるね
Did you pay attention?
気をつかった?
Let me touch your chest.
くりし触ってもらおう
It looks amazing.
すごいりだらしいです
I'm here.
い ってるよ
My hands are fine.
手は大丈夫
It's okay here, right?
ここはもう大丈夫でしょ?
Is it okay at the entrance?
入り口のところは大丈夫?
No, but it's quite widespread.
いや、でもかなり広がってはいるよ
Yeah, OK.
うん、OK
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Yes, take a nice break.
はい、すんごく休憩して
I say "nechi" every day.
毎日ねちって言ってるよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Looks like it's okay.
大丈夫そうだね
Grow up.
成長して
Have you grown up?
成長しちゃったの?
I want to put both hands firmly in it.
両手しっかり入れたいね
Have you grown?
成長した?
Yeah.
うん
Push your right foot a little.
右足ちょっと押して
oh yeah.
そうそう
a little bit
ちょっと
Remove this.
これ 外して
Leave it there for a moment.
ちょっとそのままして
I want it to stick out like that.
そのまま突き出してほしい
oh yeah.
そうそう
Why don't we do it together?
二人でやらないの?
Stick it out.
グッと突き出して
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸して
How much do you say out loud?
いっぱい声出していくら
Yeah, I'll say that.
そうそう、そう言うよ
I also have club activities.
部活も入ってるよ
This is okay.
これは大丈夫だね
There's something like that in there.
そんなぶっといの入ってるね
Look at me, properly.
こっち見て、ちゃんと
I'm here, now.
こっち入った、今
tell me.
教えて
I came here.
こっちに入った
Look here.
こ っち見て
Look at me.
こ っち見てて
That's amazing, your ass is really open.
すごいね、お尻めっちゃ開いてるよ
Then it became growth.
じゃあ成長になった
Yes, drop your foot.
そう、足落として
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Mank is okay, right?
マンクは大丈夫でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Raise your legs.
足あげて
Hold my legs.
足を持ってあげて
Hold it in your hand.
手で持って
Lift your butt up.
お尻グッと持ち上げて
I'll put it in at the end.
最後じゃ入れるよ
Give it well.
しっかりあげて
Give me your ass.
お尻あげて
It's cute.
かわいいね
terrible?
やばい?
Yeah.
うん
Hold on to your legs.
足を頑張って持ってて
This one too.
こっちも
Take it, take it, take it.
持って持って持って
Okay, then good luck.
よし、じゃあ頑張って
I'll go.
行 くからね
Raise your legs.
足あげて
Please do your best with this leg.
こっちの足頑張ってあげて
Okay, then let's go.
よし、じゃあ行くよ
Good luck with your legs.
足を頑張って
If you work hard on your legs, I'll go.
足頑張ってあげたら行ってあげるから
Give me a jerk.
グッとあげて
This one too.
こっちも
both both both.
両 方両方両方
Put your feet up, put your feet up.
足あげて足あげて
Have both.
両方持って
Raise both your legs.
両方足あげて
Are you crying?
泣いてるの?
good?
よかった?
good luck.
頑張ってね
Was it painful?
苦しかった?